stuffgate.com 2019-09-29

# Privacy Policy - StuffGate

### Introduction

The privacy of our visitors to StuffGate is important to us.

At StuffGate, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit StuffGate, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### WHOIS

We may display whois data of each supported domain, including emails, addresses and telephone numbers. These data are made available to public by many registras. We do, however, use reCaptcha service to protect email addresses from spammers and email harvesting programs. We only provide the lastest whois data and do not store the previous ones. If whois data of a domain are changed, one can requests update at our system in at most 72 hours. You can find out more about WHOIS policy by [clicking here](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Whois).

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on StuffGate to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
